Finding Aid for the Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990
Mus. Arc. 36
Conlogue, Barbara Ann, 1928-1995
2 containers (176 prints, 197 slides, 8 clippings)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990 contains 383 images and eight clippings documenting the life and career of soprano Eleanor Steber. The collection includes stock publicity photographs, but is special for the many informal snapshots of Steber at various functions throughout her career. The snapshots include photographs of a television screen during broadcasts of Steber performances.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Barbara Ann Conlogue's cousin, Joanne Oakes, in 2007-2009.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
All images have been digitized and are available in University Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Eleanor Steber was born 17 July 1916 in Wheeling, West Virginia. She made her premiere with the Metropolitan Opera in 1940 and remained with the company until 1963. She is noted for her work as the first Vanessa in Samuel Barber’s opera of that name and she also commissioned the composer for his work, Knoxville: Summer of 1915. She performed the title role of Arabella in Richard Strauss’s opera in the American premiere at the Metropolitan Opera in 1955 and sang the part of Marie in Alban Berg’s Wozzeck in the first performance by the Metropolitan Opera in 1959. Steber devoted her later years to teaching, working at the Cleveland Institute, Juilliard, and her alma mater, New England Conservatory. She established the Eleanor Steber Music Foundation to assist young singers in the early stages of their careers. Steber died in Langhorne, Pennsylvania 3 October 1990.
Barbara Ann Conlogue was a devoted fan of Eleanor Steber. She was born 23 April 1928 in New York, daughter of Donald and Mary T. (Durant) Conlogue. She grew up in Maine and Massachusetts. She attended nursing school and was employed as a nurse by Dr. Harold A. Titus of Chelmsford, Massachusetts. It is possible that it was Dr. Titus who introduced Barbara Ann Conlogue to Eleanor Steber. Barbara Ann died 27 December 1995 in Lowell, Massachusetts. [Biographical information courtesy of Joanne Oakes.]
Scope and Content Note
The Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990 contains 383 images of soprano Eleanor Steber. The collection includes stock publicity photographs, but is special for the many informal snapshots of Steber at various functions throughout her career. The snapshots include photographs of a television screen during broadcasts of Steber performances. There are eight clippings in the collection, including three obituaries.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series:
I. Prints
II. Slides
III. Clippings
Container List
- Prints, circa 1935-1979, I.; Item 001-176
  Arranged in rough chronological order.
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marguerite in Gounod's Faust, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: William Morris Agency, Inc. (Box 1, Item ES-001)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marguerite in Gounod's Faust, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-002)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marguerite in Gounod's Faust, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: De Bellis (New York, NY) (Box 1, Item ES-003)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Manon in Massenet's Manon, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-004)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Fiordiligi in Mozart's Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Halsman, Philippe (Box 1, Item ES-005)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Fiordiligi in Mozart's Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-006)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Fiordiligi in Mozart's Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-007)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Donna Anna in Mozart's Don Giovanni, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-008)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Countess Almaviva in Mozart's Nozze de Figaro, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: William Morris Agency, Inc. (Box 1, Item ES-009)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Mimi in Puccini's La Boheme, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-010)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-011)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Cio Cio San in Puccini's Madama Butterfly, 1951, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Bruno of Hollywood (New York, NY) (Box 1, Item ES-012)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Cio Cio San in Puccini's Madama Butterfly, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Bruno of Hollywood (New York, NY) (Box 1, Item ES-013)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Tosca in Puccini's Tosca, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Abresch, J. (Box 1, Item ES-014)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Rosalinda in Johann Strauss's Die Fledermaus, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-015)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume on stage as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-016)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-017)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-018)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marschallin in Richard Strauss's Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 7 x 9 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-019)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Sophie von Faninal in Richard Strauss's Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: De Bellis (New York, NY) (Box 1, Item ES-020)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Desdemona in Verdi's Otello, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-021)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Violetta in Verdi's La Traviata, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-022)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa in Wagner's Lohengrin, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-023)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa in Wagner's Lohengrin, undated, 1 5 x 7 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-024)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 7 x 9 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-025)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-026)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, 1961, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-027)
  - Eleanor Steber recital photo, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-028)
  - Eleanor Steber recital photo, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-029)
  - Eleanor Steber and Norman Farrow singing at a Bach Aria Group Concert, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-030)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified male, undated, 1 7 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-031)
  - Eleanor Steber, Edwin Bilby, and dog, undated, 1 7 1/2 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-032)
  - Eleanor Steber, Edwin Bilby, and car, undated, 1 7 1/2 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-033)
  - Eleanor Steber and Dmitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-034)
  - Eleanor Steber and Eugene Ormandy after Philadelphia Orchestra Concert, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-035)
  - Eleanor Steber and Eugene Ormandy after Philadelphia Orchestra Concert, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-036)
  - Eleanor Steber and tenor Brian Sullivan at Boston Commons, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-037)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Vanessa in Samuel Barber's Vanessa, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-038)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Vanessa in Samuel Barber's Vanessa, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-039)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Vanessa in Samuel Barber's Vanessa, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-040)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marguerite with Bill Park (right) and unidentified male, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-041)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Vanessa and Rosalind Elias as Erika in Samuel Barber's Vanessa, undated, 1 4 x 6 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-042)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Manon in Massenet's Manon, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-043)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Fiordiligi in Mozart's Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Halsman, Philippe (Box 1, Item ES-044)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Sophie and Risë Stevens as Octavian in Strauss's Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-045)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, 1956, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-046)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, 1956, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-047)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, 1956, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-048)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, 1956, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-049)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-050)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Tosca in Puccini's Tosca, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-051)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Rosalinda in Johann Strauss's Die Fledermaus, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-052)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa and Astrid Varnay as Ortrud in Wagner's Lohengrin, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-053)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage as the Empress in Richard Strauss's Frau ohne Schatten, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-054)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Desdemona in Verdi's Otello, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item ES-055)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa in Wagner's Lohengrin, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-056)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Violetta in Verdi's La Traviata, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 6 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-057)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-058)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-059)
  - Eleanor Steber in dressing room after a performance of Tosca, 1956, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-060)
  - Eleanor Steber in dressing room after a performance of Tosca, 1956, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-061)
  - Eleanor Steber in dressing room after a performance of Tosca, 1956, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-062)
  - Eleanor Steber in dressing room after a performance of Tosca, 1956, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-063)
  - Eleanor Steber in dressing room after a performance of Tosca, 1956, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-064)
  - Eleanor Steber at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-065)
  - Eleanor Steber with a projector at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-066)
  - Eleanor Steber drinking tea next to Helen Ulmer at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-067)
  - Eleanor Steber with Ann (Penny) McInnis (right) and unidentified female at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-068)
  - Eleanor Steber at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-069)
  - Eleanor Steber with three unidentified females at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-070)
  - Eleanor Steber using a projector standing next to Grace Davis Mechling at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-071)
  - Eleanor Steber with her husband Edwin Bilby at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 2 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-072)
  - Eleanor Steber with Ann (Penny) McInnis at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-073)
  - Eleanor Steber with unidentified female at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 2 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-074)
  - Eleanor Steber with coat on at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-075)
  - Eleanor Steber at a party in a hotel suite in New York City, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-076)
  - Eleanor Steber recital photo, undated, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-077)
  - Eleanor Steber about to board a plane, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-078)
  - Eleanor Steber recital photo, undated, 1 3 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-079)
  - Eleanor Steber and accompanist, James Quillian, at a concert at Furman University, Greenville, South Carolina, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Ulmer, Margaret (Box 1, Item ES-080)
  - Eleanor Steber, Lorin Maazel and unidentified male, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 2 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-081)
  - Eleanor Steber and three unidentified males, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-082)
  - Eleanor Steber in front of a window, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-083)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-084)
  - Eleanor Steber wearing a crown in front of a landscape painting, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-085)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 3 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-086)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 3 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-087)
  - Eleanor Steber signing papers at Furman University, Greenville, South Carolina, October 1954, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Ulmer, Margaret (Box 1, Item ES-088)
  - Eleanor Steber after Philadelphia Orchestra Concert, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-089)
  - Eleanor Steber on television, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-090)
  - Eleanor Steber on television with other cast members, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-091)
  - Eleanor Steber on television, singing in chair, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-092)
  - Eleanor Steber on television with unidentified male, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-093)
  - Eleanor Steber Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-094)
  - Eleanor Steber Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-095)
  - Eleanor Steber Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-096)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-097)
  - Eleanor Steber Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-098)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-099)
  - Eleanor Steber Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-100)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-101)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-102)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-103)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-104)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-105)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-106)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-107)
  - Eleanor Steber and choir Holiday Program television broadcast, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-108)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-109)
  - Eleanor Steber on a horse, undated, 1 3 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-110)
  - Eleanor Steber and Edwin Bilby, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-111)
  - Eleanor Steber and puppies, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-112)
  - Eleanor Steber in hat with Ann (Penny) McInnis (left) and Margaret Ulmer at the Caribe Hilton Hotel, San Juan, Puerto Rico, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-113)
  - Eleanor Steber with decorated plates, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-114)
  - Eleanor Steber with dog, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-115)
  - Eleanor Steber with her mother, Ida Nolte Steber, in the home of Margaret Ulmer in Greenville, South Carolina, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Ulmer, Margaret (Box 1, Item ES-116)
  - Eleanor Steber pouring tea, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-117)
  - Eleanor Steber and stuffed panda, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-118)